<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Tasks>
	<task>
		<task_id>1</task_id>
		<descp>Have you ever experienced one person’s yawning triggered almost all people around begin to yawn? Scientists in different fields have tried to explain this phenomenon. Please learn about the possible causes of the spread of yawning.</descp>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>0</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Paris attacks: Latest developments</title>
			<content>Here are the latest developments in the investigation of the deadly Paris terror attacks:
• Police conducted three massive raids in the northern Parisian suburb of Saint-Denis, home of the Stade de France national sports arena, the site of one of Friday's attacks. Two were at apartments; the third was at a church.
• Two suspects were killed -- a female suicide bomber who blew herself up and a terror suspect shot by a police sniper, authorities said.
• Seven people were arrested; authorities did not immediately identify them.
• Police sources tell CNN the raids were "right on time" because the suspects were "about to move on some kind of operation."
• The raids targeted the suspected ringleader of the deadly attacks, Abdelhamid Abaaoud, a senior Belgian counterterrorism official told CNN. The official cautioned that authorities weren't certain that Abaaoud was at any of the locations.
• Five police officers were injured and a police dog was killed, police said.</content>
		</Document>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>9</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Xbox 360 Turns 10 Today</title>
			<content>Happy birthday, Xbox 360! Microsoft's second big gaming console turns 10 years old today, as the company officially released the Xbox 360 to the United States and Canada on November 22, 2005. And, yes, it's also the big second birthday of the company's third console, the Xbox One, which came out on November 22, 2013—across 13 different markets, that is.
Marc Whitten, now the chief product officer at Sonos, was formerly the chief product officer of Xbox. He took to Twitter today to share some early memories of the good ol' Xbox 360 which, at the time of his departure in 2014, had sold around 80 million units worldwide.
The Xbox 360 has still managed to age fairly well—so much so, that gamers can now play around 100 or so Xbox 360 games on their new Xbox One consoles thanks to a recent update that added backwards compatibility for these older titles. As he (fairly) jokes, try going back and using a laptop from 2005 to see just how well that has aged over the past decade, assuming you can even do very much on it at all.
"Random fact: The wireless protocol for the controllers came out before BT was ready. We built it on top of an old cordless phone standard," Whitten wrote.
"Thank god we are done with that. When we put kiosks in Walmart at launch, SteveB got a call from the CEO, we'd taken down their wireless!"
And if today's birthday reminds you that you still have an Xbox 360 collecting dust in a room somewhere, you can get a decent amount of trade-in value for it from most retailers—especially if you take advantage of some "trade in a console, get even more credit" promotion, like the one GameStop was recently running.</content>
		</Document>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>1</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Does contagious yawning mean you're nice?</title>
			<content>We know that much of yawning is due to suggestibility -- it's infectious. You don't need to actually see a person yawn to involuntarily yawn yourself; hearing someone yawn or even reading about yawning can cause the same reaction. Chances are you'll yawn at least once while reading this article.
But contagious yawning goes beyond mere suggestibility. Recent studies show that the phenomenon is also related to our predisposition toward empathy -- the ability to understand and connect with others' emotional states. It sounds strange, but whether or not you're susceptible to contagious yawning may actually be related to how much empathy you feel for others.
So empathy is important, sure, but how could it possibly be related to contagious yawning? Leave it up to psychologists at Leeds University in England to answer that. In their study, researchers selected 40 psychology students and 40 engineering students. Each student was made to wait individually in a waiting room, along with an undercover assistant who yawned 10 times in as many minutes. The students were then administered an emotional quotient test: Students were shown 40 images of eyes and asked what emotion each one displayed.
The results of the test support the idea that contagious yawning is linked to empathy. The psychology students -- whose future profession requires them to focus on others -- yawned contagiously an average of 5.5 times in the waiting room and scored 28 out of 40 on the emotional test. The engineering students -- who tend to focus on things like numbers and systems -- yawned an average of 1.5 times and scored 25.5 out of 40 on the following test. The difference doesn't sound like much, but researchers consider it significant. Strangely, women, who are generally considered more emotionally attuned, didn't score any higher than men [source: The Telegraph].</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>2</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Why Is Yawning Contagious?</title>
			<content>Yawning when others yawn, the study suggests, is a sign of empathy and a form of social bonding. Kids don't develop this deeply rooted behavior until around age four, the study found. Kids with autism are half as likely to catch yawns. In the most severe cases, they never do.
"Emotional contagion seems to be a primal instinct that binds us together," said Molly Helt, a graduate student in clinical psychology at the University of Connecticut, Storrs. "Yawning may be part of that."
Inspiration for her study came when she tried to get her own autistic son to clear his ears on an airplane. She repeatedly yawned at him, hoping he would yawn back. He never did.
"The fact that autistic kids don't do it might mean they're really missing out on that unconscious emotional linkage to those around them," she said.
"The big thing people try to figure out in infant development is how we become humans who understand that humans have minds that are different from ours," she added. "Autistic people never sort of seem to understand that."
Fetuses begin yawning in the womb as early as 11 weeks after conception, said Robert Provine, a developmental neuroscientist at the University of Maryland, Baltimore County.
For reasons scientists still can't explain, spontaneous yawning continues throughout life. (Studies have shot down theories about yawning to bring in more oxygen.) In fact, all vertebrates yawn, including snakes and lizards.
Contagious yawning is a different story. Only humans, chimpanzees and possibly dogs have been shown to do it.
Like contagious laughter and contagious crying, scientists have theorized that contagious yawning is a shared experience that promotes social bonding. Specifically, Helt said, it could diffuse stress after a period of being on high alert and spread a feeling of calm through a group.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>3</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>How yawning spreads from brain to brain</title>
			<content>The premotor cortex initiates a person’s inadvertent reaction of laughing after hearing laughter. More specifically, a part of this area of the brain, called the PMVc area, helps trigger motor function in response to visual and auditory stimuli. It could also be the mechanism that makes you yawn when seeing others do it.
Yawning has also been linked to emotional closeness. In a study published in 2011, participants responded to the other person’s yawn much more quickly and more often than they did responding to a stranger’s.
A simple “mirroring” action could explain the contagious effects of laughter and yawning. Humans and animals are actually hardwired to demonstrate this mirroring effect. Mirror neurons are found in parts of the human brain designated to motor function, like the premotor cortex, and are the neurons that trigger responses in the premotor cortex to stimuli. They are known as the human Mirror Neuron System (hMNS).
Van Overwalle and Baetens assert there is yet another brain system involved in contagious laughter and yawning. The mentalizing system in the prefrontal cortex works with the mirroring system to process why the behavior is taking place. This is crucial to human interaction because it helps to establish empathy and encourage social bonding, which also promotes the mirroring effect.
The premotor cortex, hMNS, and mentalizing system are all linked in responding to visual and auditory stimuli. Their responses are more strongly triggered in the premotor cortex when a person interacts with someone he or she is close to. It may be instinct to mirror someone’s yawn or laugh due to the hMNS, but when two people have an emotional tie, the mentalizing system factors in to facilitate understanding and improve the relationship between them. Next time a friend tries to point a finger at you for spreading the yawning bug, know he or she is really just an affectionate fool for you.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>4</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Brain Gets Rid of Toxins During Sleep</title>
			<content>Sleep is an integral part of being healthy. Lack of sleep causes harmful physiological effects ranging from simple skin problems to serious health complications like heart disease and stroke. Although sleep needs vary from person to person and across species, the complete absence of it is fatal. An experiment on rats found that depriving them entirely of sleep resulted in their death within 11-32 days.[2] Despite research such as this, there isn’t any scientific evidence that prove the physiological causes of death by sleep deprivation.
In fact, in the rat sleep deprivation experiment, it is not entirely clear whether sleep was what caused the deaths. It is possible the methods used to keep the rats awake, an electric shock, was what killed them. A recent 2013 study on mice, however, may have found the first scientific evidence proving the physiological importance of sleep.
“We here report that sleep has a critical function in ensuring metabolic homeostasis…the restorative function of sleep may be a consequence of the enhanced removal of potentially neurotoxic waste products that accumulate in the awake central nervous system.” [1] The findings suggest sleep helps the brain get rid of toxins. With further examination, they have found that the mechanism behind this garbage collection lies in glial cells’ fluid control over cerebrospinal fluid. The brain’s glial cells expand when awake which block fluid flow and contract when asleep allowing the fluid to carry debris out of the brain into the liver for disposal. Surprisingly, pieces of protein that cause Alzheimer’s disease are among those flushed out of the mice’ brain. Many scientist were shocked by the results of this experiment and led some to redefine their views on the significance of sleep. Not only does it prove the importance of sleep, it also may revolutionize the future of Alzheimer’s disease treatment.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>5</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Hemifacial Spasm</title>
			<content>This is a condition in which there is involuntary twitching of muscles that are innervated by the seventh cranial nerve. The condition has two forms: typical and atypical. In the typical case, the twitching starts around the eye, usually the lower lid. As time progresses, the twitching spreads to include the whole lid, then the cheekbone area, then the lower jaw. As the progress is usually inexorable, the muscles in the neck become involved. In the atypical cases, the twitching starts in the lower face and progresses to involve the remainder of the facial muscles. It can sometimes be triggered by volitional contraction of certain facial muscles, especially puckering the lips or forcefully closing the eyes. Stressful situations or fatigue may also worsen the spasms. Estimates suggest that one in ten thousand people have hemifacial spasm.
A common feature is the development of a twitch that does not stop: tonus. In the eye area, this causes the eye to close, a prolonged wink, which the sufferer cannot usually oppose. The tonus phenomena lasts a few seconds, but can be prolonged.
As the twitching increases, and especially after the onset of tonus, there is often some underlying muscle weakness seen during periods of muscle relaxation.
The twitching is usually described as a sense of the lower lid moving, but may not be visible at all times. The patient usually experiences a feeling the muscles are always moving, to some degree.
The differential diagnosis of Hemifacial spasm helps to demonstrate how to make a secure diagnosis.
There are no medicines that can effectively control the spasm. Several classes of medicines (anti-spasmodics, anticonvulasants) will reduce some of the symptoms, for a time. Botulinum toxin has been advocated for symptom control. This agent is a synthetic form of a biotoxin.</content>
		</Document>
	</task>
	<task>
		<task_id>2</task_id>
		<descp>Recently the Chinese film box office record is constantly being refreshed, indicating the continuing rapid development of Chinese film market. But how much do you know about the early films? Please search for the history of film.</descp>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>1</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>History of film</title>
			<content>The History of film began in the 1890s, when motion picture cameras were invented and film production companies started to be established. Because of the limits of technology, films of the 1890s were under a minute long and until 1927 motion pictures were produced without sound. The first decade of motion picture saw film moving from a novelty to an established large-scale entertainment industry. The films became several minutes long consisting of several shots. The first rotating camera for taking panning shots was built in 1897. The first film studios were built in 1897. Special effects were introduced into film continuously, involving action moving from one sequence into another, began to be used. In 1900s, continuity of action across successive shots was achieved and the first close-up shot was introduced. Most films of this period were what came to be called "chase films". The first use of animation in movies was in 1899. The first feature length multi-reel film was a 1906 Australian production. The first successful permanent theatre showing only films was "The Nickelodeon" in Pittsburgh in 1905. By 1910, actors began to receive screen credit for their roles, and the way to the creation of film stars was opened. Regular newsreels were exhibited from 1910 and soon became a popular way for finding out the news. Overall, from about 1910, American films had the largest share of the market in Australia and in all European countries except France. New film techniques were introduced in this period including the use of artificial lighting, fire effects and low-key lighting for enhanced atmosphere during sinister scenes. As films grew longer, specialist writers were employed to simplify more complex stories derived from novels or plays into a form that could be contained on one reel and be easier to be understood by the audience, the audience that was new to this form.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>2</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>The Silent Era</title>
			<content>Initially, there were technical difficulties in synchronizing images with sound. It was clear that Edison originally intended to create a sound film system, which would not gain worldwide recognition until the release of “The Jazz Singer” in 1927. However, there was still significant interest in motion pictures for films to be produced without sound. This is referred to as the silent era of film. However, to enhance the viewers’ experience, silent films were commonly accompanied by live musicians, sound effects and even commentary spoken by the showman or projectionist. In most countries, intertitles came to be used to provide dialogue and narration for the film. However, in Japanese cinema human narration remained popular throughout the silent era. The technical problems were resolved by 1923.
Illustrated songs were a notable exception to this trend, which began in 1894 in vaudeville houses and persisted as late as the late 1930s in film theaters. Live performance or sound recordings were paired with hand-colored glass slides projected through stereopticons and similar devices. In this way, song narrative was illustrated through a series of slides whose changes were simultaneous with the narrative development. The main purpose of illustrated songs was to encourage sheet music sales, and they were highly successful with sales reaching into the millions for a single song. Later, with the birth of film, illustrated songs were used as filler material preceding films and during reel changes.
There was a non-commercial attempt. It combined the motion picture with a combination of slides and synchronize the resulting moving picture with audio. The film included hand-painted slides as well as other previously used techniques. Simultaneously playing the audio while the film was being played with a projector was required. This monumental production, released in 1915, was entitled “The Photo-Drama of Creation” and lasted eight hours.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>3</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>History of Movie Making</title>
			<content>In the year 1872, a man named Eadweard Muybridge began experimenting on capturing moving images. With an invention of his called the Zoopraxiscope, he was able to quickly project these images, creating what is known as motion photography and the first movie to ever exist.
In 1885, two men named George Eastman and William H. Walker developed the very first reel of film. Film was sensitized paper created with a gelatin emulsion. One year later it was replaced by celluloid, which was a synthetic plastic material invented in the 1870's which was used in the chemical compound cellulose nitrate.
The Kintegraph was created be Thomas Edison's British employee William Kennedy Laurie Dickenson. It was a machine that could capture a sequence of images which was similar to a camera only it automatically took a picture of the moving image every half second. The images were then placed in his other invention, the kintescope. This device had a motor and shutter mechanism that ran a loop of film past an electric light source. The spectator would then peer through a small window to see the moving image.
After these two inventions were created, the Lumiere brothers (Auguste and Louis) created a light weight hand cranked mechanism called the Cinematographe. It could take pictures and could project large images quickly when it was linked with projecting equipment familiar from magic lantern shows.
With the Cinematographe invented, German, English, Italian, British, and American inventors were becoming "hot on their heels". The race to create the next big invention that could surpass everything created this far in the history of film was heating up. The transition of film into the 1900's was stimulated by the increasing competition among the many inventors, the easy reproducibility of film, the ability to use propaganda in cinema, and in general, it's overall appeal to growing cities.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>4</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Blondie on film: capturing Debbie Harry's early years</title>
			<content>Of all the faces that define the late Seventies and early Eighties, Debbie Harry's might be the one we remember longest. After we have forgotten Cheryl Tiegs,Marisa Berenson and other supermodels of the era, we will remember her Bardot mouth, the striking triangle it made with those cheekbones. Her glam-punk aesthetic still feels modern; her unselfconsciousness predates Kate Moss by decades.
In his new book of photographs, Chris Stein/Negative - Me, Blondie, and the Advent of Punk, Harry's bandmate and former partner has collected his images from their early years together. It documents their journey from Bowery loft to global stardom, chronicling the nascent New York punk scene and beyond, as the band began to achieve success, toured with Iggy Pop and met a wider circle of people. It takes in street photography, intimate shots of Harry and snapshots of the people who crossed their paths, from Andy Warhol to William Burroughs ("He took us shooting in his barn") to BillMurray ("He was on this drinking tour, he was kinda inebriated"). There's a rawness to many of the shots; very little appears overly posed.
Stein and Harry met in 1973, when he went to see the band she sang in - all-girl trio the Stilettos. Both were children of the Sixties. "We were both at Woodstock but not together," Stein says. "We were both just plodding along living kind of parallel lives," Harry adds. "We were so close and then finally we met up on this scene."
She remembers their first meeting. "I thought that he was a complete crazy person," she says, deadpan, then revises it for him: "I thought he was really nice, a really sweet person." "I think I saw early on [in Debbie] what everybody else was seeing later," Stein says.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>5</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Amy Winehouse film earns early Oscar buzz</title>
			<content>A new trailer for "Amy," Asif Kapadia's documentary on Amy Winehouse, appeared on the Internet Wednesday, offering glimpses of the late singer during her rise to stardom and her spiral into alcoholism and drug use.
The film played at Cannes last week in an Out of Competition Midnight Screening and has received rapturous reviews. Deadline's Pete Hammond called the film an early front-runner for a best documentary Oscar, which at this point doesn't seem like a stretch. The music-themed documentaries "Searching for Sugarman" and "20 Feet From Stardom" took home Oscars in 2013 and 2014, respectively.
Winehouse rocketed to stardom in 2006 on the strength of her soul-driven album "Back to Black." Her rebellious single "Rehab" cemented her image as an unapologetic bad girl but also hinted at the drug abuse and alcoholism that quickly led to her downfall. Winehouse won five Grammys in 2008 a the first British female to do so. She died of alcohol poisoning on July 23, 2011, at the age of 27.
Kapadia, the film's director, told Indiewire in an interview that he hopes "Amy" will make people "angry" about the way Winehouse became a popular figure of fun and mockery in the years leading up to her death.
"I think there is an element of complicity and there is something that I've found, with everyone I know who's seen it: It's personal," Kapadia told Indiewire. "It's about her and you feel for her, but it's also the personal thing where you go, 'My God, I've done this. I've done that the other day. I saw something and I thought, 'That's funny. Aren't I clever when I commented on that thing or I liked that thing or I shared that thing.'"</content>
		</Document>
	</task>
	<task>
		<task_id>3</task_id>
		<descp>One of your friend is going to study abroad and you want to help her investigating the famous Ivy League in America. What’s its constitution, its origin and its development?</descp>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>1</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Ivy League</title>
			<content>The Ivy League is a collegiate athletic conference comprising sports teams from eight private institutions of higher education in the Northeastern United States. The conference name is also commonly used to refer to those eight schools as a group. The eight institutions are Brown University, Columbia University, Cornell University, Dartmouth College, Harvard University, the University of Pennsylvania, Princeton University, and Yale University. The term Ivy League has connotations of academic excellence, selectivity in admissions, and social elitism.
While the term was in use as early as 1933, it only became official after the formation of the NCAA Division I athletic conference in 1954. Seven of the eight schools were founded during the United States colonial period; the exception is Cornell, which was founded in 1865. Ivy League institutions account for seven of the nine Colonial Colleges chartered before the American Revolution, the other two being Rutgers University and College of William and Mary.
Ivy League schools are generally viewed as some of the most prestigious, and are ranked among the best universities worldwide. All eight universities place in the top sixteen of the U.S. News and World Report 2015 university rankings, including the top four schools and six of the top eleven. U.S. News has named a member of the Ivy League as the best national university in each of the past fifteen years ending with the 2015 rankings: Princeton eight times, Harvard twice and the two schools tied for first five times.
Undergraduate enrollments range from about 4,000 to 14,000, making them larger than those of a typical private liberal arts college and smaller than a typical public state university. Total enrollments, including graduate students, range from approximately 6,100 at Dartmouth to over 20,000 at Columbia, Cornell, Harvard, and Penn. Ivy League financial endowments range from Brown's $3 billion to Harvard's $36.4 billion.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>2</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Origin of the name</title>
			<content>Students have long revered the ivied walls of older colleges. "Planting the ivy" was a customary class day ceremony at many colleges in the 1800s. In 1893 an alumnus told The Harvard Crimson, "In 1850, class day was placed upon the University Calendar.... the custom of planting the ivy, while the ivy oration was delivered, arose about this time." At Penn, graduating seniors started the custom of planting ivy at a university building each spring in 1873 and that practice was formally designated as "Ivy Day" in 1874. Ivy planting ceremonies are reported for Yale, Simmons, Bryn Mawr and many others. Princeton's "Ivy Club" was founded in 1879.
The first usage of Ivy in reference to a group of colleges is from sportswriter Stanley Woodward (1895–1965).
The first known instance of the term Ivy League being used appeared in The Christian Science Monitor on February 7, 1935. Several sportswriters and other journalists used the term shortly later to refer to the older colleges, those along the northeastern seaboard of the United States, chiefly the nine institutions with origins dating from the colonial era, together with the United States Military Academy (West Point), the United States Naval Academy, and a few others. These schools were known for their long-standing traditions in intercollegiate athletics, often being the first schools to participate in such activities. However, at this time, none of these institutions made efforts to form an athletic league.
A common folk etymology attributes the name to the Roman numeral for four (IV), asserting that there was such a sports league originally with four members. The Morris Dictionary of Word and Phrase Origins helped to perpetuate this belief. The supposed "IV League" was formed over a century ago and consisted of Harvard, Yale, Princeton, and a fourth school that varies depending on who is telling the story.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>3</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Ivy League Athletics and Sport</title>
			<content>In 1945, the first “Ivy Group Agreement” was signed. This agreement covered the sport of football only. The agreement outlined the eligibility requirements for players from these colleges, including academic standards and financial aid. It was the first agreement that outlined the common practices required for sporting events for intercollegiate competitions. This agreement led to the founding of the Ivy League in February 1954. This agreement was developed because of the intercollegiate sports shared between these universities.
The unique aspect of the colleges and universities in the Ivy League is that they were all involved in sporting events with each other for the last six decades. Each was considered allies in college sports because of the established leagues in ice hockey, baseball, basketball, and swimming. In addition, the Heptagonal Games Association was formed which covered several sport leagues, including track and field, baseball, and swimming. The athletic directors of the Ivy League schools grew accustomed to working with each other, and thus the term Ivy League was created.
Today, the Ivy League is nationally recognized for its success and high standards in academics and sports. Despite national pressures on intercollegiate rules and requirements, the Ivy League has been successful in competing in Division I athletics. From the 1956–1957 season through the 2010–2011 season, the Ivy League has won 43 NCAA team championships and 174 NCAA individual/event championships. Each year, numerous athletes are named to All-America teams and several earn postgraduate scholarships. Ivy League colleges are in the top 15 rankings academically in the U.S. They are often known for their attendance by numerous political figures in this country. Students accepted into the Ivy League earn a prestige reward associated with the names of these colleges. Not only do these college names stand out on resumes, the competitiveness of the sports is among the top in the country.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>4</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>To avoid debt, student dumps Ivy League schools for Alabama</title>
			<content>A star student from Memphis, Tennessee, who was accepted to all eight of America’s prestigious Ivy League schools has turned them all down and is headed south to the academically humble-if-football-proud, University of Alabama instead.
Ronald Nelson graduates with a 4.58 weighted GPA, 2260 out of 2400 SAT score and 15 AP classes. He was also a national merit scholar, president of his high school class and a standout alto saxophone player, Business Insider reports.
“With people being in debt for years and years, it wasn’t a burden that Ronald wanted to take on and it wasn’t a burden that we wanted to deal with for a number of years after undergraduate,” Ronald Nelson Sr. told Business Insider. “We can put that money away and spend it on his medical school, or any other graduate school.”
Nelson will be part of the University Fellows Experience at Alabama. USE is an elite honors program that only takes 8-10 students every year from 1,000 applicants.
“It was kind of amazing being around so many like-minded students, which is why I think I’ll be able to have a similar situation (to an Ivy League school), considering the type of students they’re attracting,” Nelson told Business Insider.
“Stories like Nelson’s are becoming more common as America’s most prestigious schools continue to grow financially out of reach for more and more students,” noted John Levine in Mic. “Over the last 40 years, college expenses have been rising at a breathtaking pace. Since 1978, college costs have skyrocketed more than 1,100 percent. Today, the 10 most expensive colleges in the United States all cost more than $60,000 a year. Predictably too, student loan debt has been growing in America every year since at least 1992, reaching more than $35,000 per average borrower in 2014.”</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>5</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>The Disadvantages of an Elite Education</title>
			<content>It didn’t dawn on me that there might be a few holes in my education until I was about 35. I’d just bought a house, the pipes needed fixing, and the plumber was standing in my kitchen. There he was, a short, beefy guy with a goatee and a Red Sox cap and a thick Boston accent, and I suddenly learned that I didn’t have the slightest idea what to say to someone like him. So alien was his experience to me, so unguessable his values, so mysterious his very language, that I couldn’t succeed in engaging him in a few minutes of small talk before he got down to work. Fourteen years of higher education and a handful of Ivy League degrees, and there I was, stiff and stupid, struck dumb by my own dumbness. “Ivy retardation,” a friend of mine calls this. I could carry on conversations with people from other countries, in other languages, but I couldn’t talk to the man who was standing in my own house.
It’s not surprising that it took me so long to discover the extent of my miseducation, because the last thing an elite education will teach you is its own inadequacy. As two dozen years at Yale and Columbia have shown me, elite colleges relentlessly encourage their students to flatter themselves for being there, and for what being there can do for them. The advantages of an elite education are indeed undeniable. You learn to think, at least in certain ways, and you make the contacts needed to launch yourself into a life rich in all of society’s most cherished rewards. To consider that while some opportunities are being created, others are being cancelled and that while some abilities are being developed, others are being crippled is, within this context, not only outrageous, but inconceivable.</content>
		</Document>
	</task>
	<task>
		<task_id>4</task_id>
		<descp>Dinosaurs roamed the Earth for 160 million years until their sudden die-off about 65.5 million years ago. There are many hypotheses about dinosaur extinction and please learn several of them in the following passages.</descp>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>1</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Asteroid Impact Hypothesis</title>
			<content>It is widely agreed that a giant asteroid or comet struck Earth 65 million years ago. Dinosaur extinction came quickly after this collision and the shape of life on Earth changed forever.
Scientists conclude that for months, dense clouds of dust blocked the sun's rays. Without enough sunshine, Earth was darkened and cooled to deadly levels for most plants and many animals. Then, when the dust finally settled, greenhouse gases created by the impact caused temperatures to increase sharply above pre-impact levels.
In just a few years, according to this hypothesis, these frigid and heated climatic extremes caused the extinction of not just the dinosaurs, but of up to 70 percent of all plants and animals living at the time.
There are several evidences supporting the asteroid impact hypothesis.
Firstly, a 150-kilometer-wide crater lies just off the Yucatan peninsula. Scientists calculate that it was caused by a 10-kilometer-wide asteroid or comet traveling 30 kilometers per second. Scientists have also concluded that the impact that created this crater occurred 65 million years ago. The date matches perfectly to the date of the dinosaur extinction.
Secondly, the level of a rare metal attests this hypothesis. The metal iridium is very rare on Earth's surface but is more common in asteroids and in molten rock deep within the planet. Scientists have discovered levels of iridium 30 times greater than average in the Cretaceous/Tertiary (KT) boundary. This boundary is the layer of sedimentary rock laid down at the time of the dinosaur extinction.
Besides, pieces of once-molten rock are evidence of an powerful explosion, which is powerful enough to instantly melt bedrock and propel it more than a hundred miles from its origin. 
Fractured Crystals and fossil record are other two evidences for the asteroid impact hypothesis.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>2</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>Extinction of Dinosaurs</title>
			<content>Scientists have argued for a long time that the extinction of the dinosaurs was caused by climatic changes associated with slow changes in the positions of continents and seas resulting from plate movements. 
Data from diverse sources indicate that the Late Cretaceous climate was milder than today’s. The days were not too hot, and the nights were not too cold. The summers were not too warm, and the winters were not too frigid. The shallow seas on the continents probably adjusted the temperature of the nearby air, keeping it relatively constant.
At the end of the Cretaceous, the geological record shows that these seaways retreated from the continents back into the major ocean basins. No one knows why. Over a period of about 100,000 years, while the seas pulled back, climates around the world became dramatically more extreme: warmer days, cooler nights; hotter summers, colder winters. Perhaps dinosaurs could not tolerate these extreme temperature changes and became extinct.
Although initially appealing, the hypothesis of a simple climatic change is insufficient to explain all the data. For example, it failed to explain why the cold-blooded animals could survive the freezing winters and torrid summers.
Dissatisfaction with conventional explanations for dinosaur extinctions led to a new hypothesis. Scientists hypothesized that a single large asteroid, about 10 to 15 kilometers across, collided with Earth. The resulting fallout created a thin layer of clay between Cretaceous rock layers and Cenozoic rock layers. Their calculations show that the impact produced a dust cloud that cut off sunlight for several months. Without enough sunlight, surface temperatures on continents decreased to below freezing. It also caused acid rain and significantly raised long-term global temperatures through the greenhouse effect. This disruption of food chain and climate would have eliminated the dinosaurs in less than fifty years.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>3</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>How did dinosaurs become extinct</title>
			<content>Dinosaurs became extinct about 65 million years ago at the end of the Cretaceous period. About 70% of all animal life on Earth died out during this period and scientists call it a mass extinction. It wasn’t the first mass extinction in Earth’s history and it probably won’t be the last!
Having existed for 165 million years, why did dinosaurs die out? There are many different theories about why this happened. We will probably never know exactly what has happened, which means that scientists will continue to disagree and come up with different dinosaur extinction theories.
Some of the plausible and popular theories are listed as follows.
Ice Age Theory: Now and again, the Earth cools into periods which are called Ice Ages. As dinosaurs were thought to be cold blooded, it would have been hard for them to cope with such cold conditions. For example, if large parts of the planet were covered in ice, then there would have been little or no plants for herbivorous dinosaurs to eat. However, there is no real evidence of an ice age at this time.
Volcano Theory: There was massive volcanic activity between 63 and 67 million years ago, particularly on the Deccan Plateau in western India. This, again, would have caused a massive change in climate, which dinosaurs would have found hard to adapt to.
Competition from Other Animals: Fossils of small mammals have been found from 65 million years ago. It is possible that these small Cretaceous animals started to compete with dinosaurs, for example, stealing and eating dinosaur eggs. However, no one is sure whether mammals caused dinosaur extinction, or they thrived because dinosaurs were no longer around. 
Disease: It is possible that a disease spread through the whole dinosaur population causing their extinction.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>4</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>The Cambrian Explosion</title>
			<content>During a geologically short 100-million-year period, all modern animal groups evolved. This rapid origin and diversification of animals is often referred to as “the Cambrian explosion.” Scientists have asked important questions about this explosion for more than a century. Why did it occur so late in the history of Earth? Why doesn’t the fossil record document the series of evolutionary changes during the evolution of animals? Why did animal life evolve so quickly? Scientists continue to search the fossil record for answers to these questions.
One interpretation about the absence of fossils during this important 100-million-year period is that early animals were soft bodied. Fossilization of soft-bodied animals is much more difficult than fossilization of hard-bodied animals. Though it is hard for soft-bodied animals to fossilize, it does occur. In fact, fossil beds containing soft-bodied animals have been known for many years.
A fossil formation containing both soft-bodied and hard-bodied animals provides evidence of the result of the Cambrian explosion. This fossil formation is called the Burgess Shale. These fossil beds provide evidence of about 32 modern animal groups. There are also about 20 other animal body forms, which are different from any modern animals that they cannot be assigned to any one of the modern groups. The Burgess Shale formation also has fossils of many extinct representatives of modern animal groups. 
Fossil formations like the Burgess Shale show that evolution cannot always be thought of as a slow progression. The Cambrian explosion involved rapid evolutionary diversification, followed by the extinction of many unique animals. Why was this evolution so rapid? No one really knows. Many scientists believe that it was because so many resources were available with almost no competition from existing species.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>5</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>Role of Play in Development</title>
			<content>Play is a developmental characteristic of animals. Why animals play is still a matter debated in the research area, and the reasons may not be the same for every species that plays. Determining the functions of play is difficult because the functions may be long-term. In other words, the beneficial effects of play may not show up until the animal's adulthood.
Play is usually very active, involving movement in space and, at times, noisemaking. Therefore, it results in the loss of fuel or energy. Another potential cost of this activity is greater exposure to predators since play is attention-getting behavior. Great activities also increase the risk of injury.
The benefits of play must outweigh costs, or play would not have evolved, according to Darwin' s theory. Some of the potential benefits relate directly to the healthy development of the brain and nervous system. Active play may provide necessary stimulation to the growth of cell connections in the brain.
Play also stimulates the development of the muscle tissues and may help practice movements needed for survival. Prey species, like young deer or goats, for example, typically play by performing sudden flight movements and turns, whereas predator species, such as cats, practice stalking, pouncing, and biting.
Play allows a young animal to explore its environment and practice skill in comparative safety. Play can also provide practice in social behaviors. Learning appropriate social behaviors is especially important for species that live in groups. For example, young monkeys needed to learn to control selfishness and aggression and to understand the give-and-take involved in social groups.
Of course there is a danger that play may potentially lead to aggression. Thus, many species have evolved clear signals to depict playfulness. Dogs, for example, will wag their tails to indicate "what follows is just for play."</content>
		</Document>
	</task>
	<task>
		<task_id>5</task_id>
		<descp>For the first time in three years, leaders from China, Japan and South Korea met in Seoul in Nov 2015. What did they concern during their meeting and what did they reach as agreements?</descp>
        <Document>
			<doc_id>1</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>South Korea, China, Japan vow to strengthen ties at sixth trilateral summit in Seoul</title>
			<content>South Korean president Park Geun-hye, Chinese premier Li Keqiang and Japanese premier Shinzo Abe discussed a wide range of topics during a 90-minute meeting in Seoul. The topics ranged from free trade to the threat of North Korea's nuclear weapons program.
No substantive breakthrough had been expected. Because the meeting had been seen more as a symbolic statement of intent by North-East Asia's three largest economies. They all stand to reap significant diplomatic and economic gains from closer ties.
"We shared the view that trilateral cooperation has been completely restored on the occasion of this summit," they said in a lengthy joint statement after the meeting.
The three countries began holding annual summits in 2008. However, the souring of Japan's relations with its two neighbours over issues dating back to World War II triggered a lengthy hiatus after the last meeting in 2012.
The focus on Sunday was on economic ties, with China especially keen to strengthen trade links. It tries to inject fresh momentum into its slowing economy.
The joint statement included a commitment to sealing a trilateral free-trade agreement. This agreement would provide a counterpoint to the new US-led Pacific trade pact, of which China and South Korea are not members.
Also high on the agenda was North Korea, which has nuclear weapons ambitions which worry and threaten all three countries, including China, the North's main diplomatic protector and economic benefactor.
The leaders reaffirmed their "firm opposition" to the development of nuclear weapons on the Korean peninsula as well as any action that could raise tensions or violate UN resolutions.
Pyongyang has recently hinted at a space rocket launch which would contravene a UN ban on its use of ballistic missile technology.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>2</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>China, Japan and South Korea held 6th Trilateral summit after 3 years</title>
			<content>The Prime Minister of Japan Shinzo Abe, the Premiere of China Li Kequiang and President of South Korea Guen hye held a trilateral meeting on November 1, 2015 at Seoul. This was the 6th trilateral summit between the three countries. The three leaders discussed the setting up of RCEP (Regional Comprehensive Economic Partnership). It would be a free trade agreement comprising 16 countries. The proposed free trade agreement grouping would include India and 10 other countries of ASEAN (Association of South East Asian Nations). China has been the main proponent behind establishing such a regional trade bloc. It would be the world’s largest trading bloc comprising about 3.4 billion of the world population.
The leaders of the three countries also discussed the issue regarding conflict between South Korea and North Korea, and affirmed their commitment to work towards nuclear disarmament of North Korea which presents a ever present threat to the Korean Peninsula. The three leaders also committed to increase trade and commerce between their respective countries. This is the first time that the annual trilateral summit between China, Japan and South Korea were held on November 1, 2015 after a gap of 3 years. The Prime Minister of Japan Shinzo Abe congratulated and credited the restoration of the trilateral summit to the President of South Korea.
All the three countries China, Japan and South Korea are the major economies in the region and in the wake of slow economic recovery of Europe and USA, Japan and South Korea are viewing to strenghthen economic cooperation between themselves. Both Japan and South Korea are traditionally close partners of USA in the region and both have a history of confrontational relations with China. Japan and China are involved in a territorial dispute, while China’s support to North Korea has been a major issue in relation of China with South Korea.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>3</doc_id>
			<relevance>1</relevance>
			<title>China-Japan-South Korea summit restored after 3.5-year hiatus</title>
			<content>The trilateral cooperation mechanism consisting of China, Japan and South Korea is restored on Sunday with the resumption of the leaders' meeting after a three-and-half-year suspension due to heightened regional tensions.
The sixth trilateral summit in Seoul came as relations between Japan and the two neighbors have started thawing. It also followed active coordination of South Korea, the rotating host of the sixth gathering.
"We share the view that trilateral cooperation has been completely restored on the occasion of this summit. It held almost three and a half years after the fifth trilateral summit held in May 2012," said a joint declaration issued after the meeting.
According to the document, the three countries reaffirmed their commitment to hold the trilateral meeting on a regular basis.
Chinese Premier Li Keqiang, Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe and South Korean President Park Geun-hye attended the summit. They also jointly met with the press and attended a business summit.
The China-Japan-South Korea summit had taken place annually from 2008 to 2012. However, it bogged down due to Japanese provocations on historical and territorial issues that angered both China and South Korea.
The joint declaration also stressed the need to improve bilateral ties. Deepening trilateral cooperation will also in turn contribute to each bilateral relations, and to peace and stability in Northeast Asia.
Citing the recent rough patch of China-Japan interaction, Li said the two countries both know the causes. They should summarize the past and draw lessons from it.
They need to properly handle the sensitive issues in bilateral political relations. They should be under the spirit of looking at history squarely and taking history as a mirror. They should keep a firm grasp on the overall development of their strategic relationship of mutual benefit, he said.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>4</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>PM Modi proposes $1 billion line of credit for connectivity with ASEAN</title>
			<content>Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday proposed a USD one billion line of credit to promote projects that support physical and digital connectivity between India and ASEAN.
"Connectivity is the pathway to shared prosperity. The Trilateral Highway project is making good progress. It should be completed by 2018," Modi said in his opening remarks at the India-ASEAN Summit here.
"We also propose to commit a Line of Credit of 1 billion US dollars to promote projects. They support physical and digital connectivity between India and ASEAN," he said.
ASEAN grouping includes Brunei, Cambodia, Indonesia, Laos, Malaysia, Myanmar, the Philippines, Singapore, Thailand and Vietnam.
“As in the past, we place special emphasis on our partnership with Cambodia, Laos, Myanmar and Vietnam. Our partnership with them in capacity building projects will expand. In addition, we intend to create a Project Development Fund to develop manufacturing hubs in CLMV countries," he said.
Modi noted that science, technology and innovation constituted a vital pillar of cooperation and supported economic partnership. He said India would enlarge the ASEAN-India Science and Technology Development Fund from the current USD one million to USD 5 million.
Modi told ASEAN members that New Delhi also intend to set-up an ASEAN-India Innovation Platform to facilitate commercialisation of low cost technologies, technology transfer and collaborative R&amp;D projects.
"Our cooperative project in Space, to be located in Vietnam, is now making concrete progress. I assure you of its early completion," he said.
India also offered ASEAN its indigenously developed GPS Aided Geo Augmented Navigation or GAGAN services. It provides advanced navigation and location assistance and information facilities.
Modi arrived here early today on a three-day visit to Malaysia to attend the ASEAN-India and East Asia summits.</content>
		</Document>
		<Document>
			<doc_id>5</doc_id>
			<relevance>0</relevance>
			<title>[Analysis] At sixth summit, S. Korea and China ward off tensions on the peninsula</title>
			<content>During a summit at the Great Hall of the People in Beijing on Sep. 2, South Korean President Park Geun-hye and Chinese President Xi Jinping stated that they oppose any activity that causes tensions on the Korean peninsula. This is being taken to mean opposition to a show of force by North Korea that could occur on Oct. 10, the 70th anniversary of the foundation of the Korean Workers’ Party.
Though the meeting on Sep. 2 was the sixth summit between Park and Xi, it attracted more attention than any previous meeting. Since the meeting was the result of Park’s decision to defy American displeasure by becoming the only US ally to attend a Chinese military review commemorating the 70th anniversary of the victory over Japan in World War II, there were quiet expectations that the outcome of the meeting would live up to the boldness of her decision.
The press release provided by the Blue House on Wednesday detailing the results of the summit contains a number of phrases and agreements that are noticeably different from previous summits. China appears to have made an effort to accept South Korean demands to some extent. But there is also doubt that this will lead to a fundamental change in the areas of inter-Korean relations or the North Korean nuclear issue.
In regard to relations on the Korean Peninsula, including the North Korean nuclear issue, the statement includes language that can be understood as a request for North Korea to refrain from launching a missile on Oct. 10.
“Both sides emphasized that the Sep. 19 Joint Statement and the related resolutions by the UN Security Council should be faithfully implemented and in relation to this that they oppose any action whatsoever that increases tensions,” the press release said.</content>
		</Document>
	</task>
</Tasks>